Translated by Sikkon
Translated by Mou
A la ila la j囉
I'm a silver pink
The time has come to an end, so let's get together
You and you, you and you
If we love each other, we'll be together
We'll be together, so let's get together
Good luck
We're in trouble
I can't believe things are going to happen
From the time when the coin accumulated,
We've become more aware of the huge castle
If it was up to us, we would have been moved to a strange world
I don't know where we are
I don't know why the world is coming back
Let's start from now
The
Emotions of KyōRyu!
A
What are you doing, Kisuo?
You don't have to think about it yet, do you?
It's good, isn't it?
It's fun to go anywhere, too, right?
I wonder if it's interesting.
What?
Where is it?
Are you all right, Udoku?
The time machine is gone?
I can't go back to the rest of the world!
I'm going to fail again!
What are you saying?
You said you were going to fail in a difficult place,
but didn't you all do it?
I did it!
Thank you so much for coming here.
I'll give you a drink if you come here.
That's right.
It's good.
It's good, Kowri.
It's better to drink delicious coffee if you do this.
Where are you going, Udoku?
I'm always worried about you.
Are you all doing your best here?
That guy is a tough guy.
He has a special order.
I don't want to be with him.
Hey, everyone!
I'm going to drink today too!
Baby!
No, I'll take care of the time machine.
I won't let you get to the top of my heart.
I'll take care of you!
You'll lose all of that.
That's it!
That's right!
I'm waiting, Udoku.
That's not good.
What are you doing here?
I'm just worried about Eikutsu.
That's right. Let's take care of everyone.
Take care?
Maybe we can't find a treasure here.
Maybe we can find a treasure here.
Hey, hey, are you looking for a treasure?
Huh?
I know the treasure of the treasure.
I see.
Really?
I think we can find a treasure here.
I can't see anything like that, but...
I'll go with you.
Let's go.
Wow, that's amazing, Kusar!
There are various types of treasures.
There are various types of treasures here.
If you're here, you won't be able to find a treasure.
I see.
Do you really think so?
I'll find a treasure there.
Really?
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
I want to find a treasure here.
I still like it.
I thought it was a treasure, but it's pretty good.
Even if I do that, this treasure is called a treasure.
So, I'm going to find a treasure here.
It's a treasure.
Hey, you guys.
There are various types of treasures here.
This treasure is a treasure.
What is it?
Is there treasure that you can see here?
I don't know that.
It's a jungle treasure that I've eaten yesterday.
I'm going to help you.
Help me, One.
Oh, baby.
It's too weak to say that.
Now, let's go.
I got it.
Yes.
It's not a treasure of humans, it's a treasure.
I got it.
Don't you think it's a treasure?
It's a treasure.
Huh?
I'm so excited again.
Where did you go?
Mom, don't you know the rules?
If you know the rules, I'll be there.
Ah, that's nice.
This Erica has a special head in her ear.
It's true.
Hey, just a moment.
You and I were together.
Ah, what's wrong?
You're such a fool, aren't you?
You're not a fool.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
The rules are the rules.
Did you fall into the trap of a lot of people?
Huh? Did you go there?
It's like a lie.
I can't get close to everyone.
I don't believe it.
What are you saying?
You said you'd be fine.
That's why you're here.
How do you think you're just a fool?
Everyone's going to be fine.
What are you saying?
Oh, well.
I knew you'd be fine if you didn't get close to the rules.
That's why I'm glad.
You guys, hurry up and be careful.
It's just that you don't have to do it again.
But you're amazing.
You look like a fool.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's okay.
In here, there's not a lot of food left.
When I was eating, I was feeling anxious.
Hmm.
Oh, that's true.
I want to eat coffee.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Did you have a lot of coffee?
I found a good one.
I'll make a special coffee for you.
Don't you think you're good at it?
I think you're really good at it.
That's what you're saying.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
I'm going to start.
I'm going to have a drink.
Ha, ha, ha.
Don't worry about me.
I'm going to have a drink.
I'm always here.
Yeah, right?
I won't lose.
You'll be weak.
You won't lose.
Oh, I don't understand.
I'm not trying to make that one.
I have it.
I'm going to eat.
I'll eat.
Well, I'll eat.
Wait a minute!
That's right, it's Ulul and Sotsuki.
Good boy! Good boy!
Ah, you're back.
Good, you're back.
It's been a long time since we've been together for a long time.
Ulul!
Mom, mom!
That's the first time we've been together.
The first time!
Look, Ulul is not just Sotsuki, but he's really a pretty good player.
I guess that's right.
I can't do this anymore!
Just you and me, Oba-san!
You and I, our Ulul and I have just one more thing to do.
There's no such thing as one.
It's a common thing that we've been to the village of green forests in Ulul and in the past.
It's been a long time since we've been together.
Oh, the village? Oh, that's a good place.
Where are you hiding, Goji?
Huh?
I don't want to see you.
I've just been hiding.
I wonder what's going on.
I wonder if Uru-Uru's ability is right.
Yes.
I can see something else when I'm born.
I wonder if Uru-Uru's ability is right.
Yes, Uru.
Do you think we should let you act like this?
It's
My God!
What? Is this the last one?
Oh, that's right. The blueberry jam is over now.
Muka, it's not over yet, so let's eat slowly.
It's not only coffee, but you have to make jam as sweet as you like.
No, no! The jam is coming out as sweet as you like!
Let's try it.
It's true.
You don't believe in anything like that.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
You're making a brand that you like.
Let's go to my store!
Let's go!
I don't want to eat too much.
It's a life that's not easy to make.
That's right. It's not easy to make a brand.
Hey, it's not easy to make a brand.
I'm not.
It's not easy to make a brand that you like.
Then, let's go to my store.
My store?
My store!
I've never seen a store like this before!
It's over here.
There's a supermarket here.
Oh?
Where are you going, Muka Muka?
I'm going to the ice cream shop.
I'm so happy.
Isn't it nice?
I'm going to the ice cream shop too.
I'm going too.
Let's all eat up the ice cream shop before we go to the ice cream shop.
Muka, I just can't eat you either.
My shop?
There it is!
I'm going to the ice cream shop too.
Muka, I won't attacks you.
I won't attack you.
I don't want to hit you.
Yay!
It's a really fun document!
Let's look into it.
Galaine!
Done.
You're making it easy.
Galaine!
I'm going to eat it!
You ate it again, didn't you?
What's wrong with that?
It's a strange thing to eat.
I'm going to eat it!
Are you okay?
I ate the most.
What's wrong with you?
I'm not doing anything!
I'm kidding!
Are you kidding?
I'm not here anymore!
I really wanted to make you a cat by the way.
Lucky!
I have a wonderful weather for this weather.
I want to make you a fresh and sunny weather.
And I can make you a happy one!
Muka, Muka, you should have put them in the bathroom.
It's not like you put them in the bathroom.
Muka, you're going to have a bad night now!
Don't be so cowardly!
Muka, you can't be the one who's supposed to be jealous of us.
Ah!
Ah?
Maybe you don't believe what you're trying to do, right?
Mugamu!
Don't do that! It's because you can't let go of your hands!
But it's a wonderful sky!
Mugamu!
You can't do that, right?
This is the first time I've ever done this!
Mugamu!
Ah!
The day of the year has finally come!
The morning has finally come!
I was born a day before.
I wonder if I believed in the truth.
If I didn't believe it, I wouldn't have been able to see.
I wonder if it's better to believe in something like that.
Gya, gya!
When I was young,
I was always there for you,
and I was always there for you.
Gya, gya!
Oh, it's too small!
This is the star of the sea, Muka Muka.
Muka Muka!
Where are you going?
That's the opposite of us.
Muka Muka!
Where are you going?
What is that?
Sweet!
It's like blueberry!
Muka Muka did it!
Muka Muka!
Where are you going?
You're going to get bored of it?
I see.
I saw you.
I think it's strange.
I thought you were here.
Muka Muka!
Good morning.
What is it?
It's a little dirty.
It became a difficult thing to do with your hand.
I disappeared because I went to see the stars.
Huh? I don't know what kind of meaning it is.
It's not a fairy tale.
You make a fool of the starry sky.
Huh? I don't remember anything.
It's the first time.
Let's go back home.
Maybe I'm back in the air.
Oh, it's gone.
Yo-chan, maybe I went to that forest by myself.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Is this the forest of the moon?
If I go in here, I want to get out of here.
Yo-chan, what should I do?
I see.
Even if I go in the inside, I can get out of here.
Hurry up and go to the entrance of the starry sky.
What are you doing in the air?
Now,
Is it a place where you eat so much?
How can I get out of here?
Hey, Ui-chan, Ui-chan!
Dad!
Here!
I'm here!
Ui-chan!
How is it? It's good for your eyes.
I'm going home.
Ui-chan, Ui-chan!
That's right.
I haven't found Ui-chan yet.
I can't hear everyone's voice.
What should I do?
I'm going to get out of here!
No!
Uuuh...
I'm going to get out of here and get out of here!
I'm going to get out of here!
Ui-chan, Ui-chan!
What's this light?
Dad!
Oh!
Ui-chan!
You're good, right?
You scare me!
I know you saved us just by getting out of here.
Ui-chan...
Ui-chan, Ui-chan!
Who is the power of the Miracle?
Now, it's ready for the jump!
Yeah!
That's great!
Now, it's time for the jump!
If you go to that forest, you'll get the Blue Fairy!
Just a little bit! I'll try too!
Yeah!
Let's do it!
Failed! Failed! Failed! Failed! Failed! Failed!
Paradise!
Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out!
Let's do it!
No matter who, no matter who, we're all going to die!
Let's go to that forest!
So, oh yeah, there is always a song that is written
I'm singing the song and singing it
These are the changes
What is this? It's a good song
It's because the star of the stars is a heart
Bion, bion, bion, bion, bion, bion
I love you so much, so much, so much, so much
I love you so much, so much, so much, so much, so much
I'm looking forward to that
I love you so much, so much, so much, so much, so much, so much, so much, so much, so much, so much, so much, so much, so much,
A dumplings
Finishing the first piece
I can't help but sleepy
A thank you whenever you come
What's wrong?
Where's this place?
You turned this have to go to later
I told you to go to the picnic, so I didn't go anywhere!
Next time, I'll go to the Mugamukapara Dice.
I'll go to the picnic, and I'll go to the Mugamukapara Dice!